One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Is Conis gonna be alright?
‫هل ستكون كونيس بخير؟‬
She wound up as an accomplice because she tried to save us!
‫حاولت إنقاذنا لكنها أصبحت متواطئة في نهاية المطاف‬
She's gonna have hell to pay for sure!
‫لن تفلت من العقاب بالتأكيد‬
That old Sky Knight said he'd look after her, but...
‫قال فارس السماء العم إنه سيعتني بها، ولكن...‬
Nah, he's weird, but I don't think he's a bad guy.
‫لا يبدو ذلك العم الغريب رجلًا سيّئًا‬
We don't have a choice.
‫ما باليد حيلة‬
I wanna protect her, but we can't take her with us, either.
‫أود حمايتها ولكن لا يمكننا أخذها معنا‬
C'mon, this thing's so slow...
‫إنّ هذا لبطيءٌ حقًّا!‬
Of course it is. It's way heavier than a waver.
‫لأنّه أثقل بأضعاف من الويفر‬
Quit complaining!
‫لا تتذمّر‬
Adventure on God's Island
‫مغامرة في جزيرة الإله‬
Hey, look! What's with that humongous forest?!
‫انظرا، ما تلك الغابة العملاقة؟‬
Is that Upper Yard?!
‫أهذه الساحة العليا؟‬
Amazing! Was there a forest like this on the map?!
‫مذهل، أكانت هذه الغابة موجودةٌ على الخريطة؟‬
Well, the map did show a forest, but it was nothing like what's in front of us.
‫كانت هناك واحدة بالخريطة ولكنّها ليست كهذه‬
This one's normal.
‫مجرد غابة عاديّة‬
People from 200 years ago had that map, right?
‫كانت الخريطة في حوزة أشخاصٍ قبل مئتي عام، أليس كذلك؟‬
It might have been old even back then.
‫لعلها كانت تُعتبر قديمة في وقتهم‬
It'd take at least 1,000 years for trees to grow this massive!
‫تحتاج هذه الأشجار لا يقلّ عن ألف سنة لتصبح عملاقة هكذا‬
That's true...
‫فعلًا...‬
They sure are big trees!
‫إنّها أشجار ضخمة حقًّا‬
I wanna climb 'em!
‫أودّ تسلقها!‬
It's the entrance!
‫ها هو المدخل‬
Well, if we're gonna turn back, now's our chance.
‫حسنٌ، لا نملك إلّا هذه الفرصة إن كنّا سنتراجع‬
You ready, Usopp?
‫أأنت مستعد يا أوسوب؟‬
Huh? W-Well, I wouldn't mind if we went back–
‫إن كان ذلك ممكنًا، فأودّ العودة...‬
Let's go!
‫لننطلق!‬
You weren't even gonna listen to me!
‫لم تستمع لي حتى‬
I wanna go back...
‫أريد العودة...‬
Something's here!
‫يوجد شيءٌ هناك!‬
Well, it is a forest!
‫هذا واضح، إنّها غابة‬
Yeah, it is.
‫صحيح‬
N-N-No, just hold on! Look around you!
‫لا، لا، تمهلا! انظرا حواليكما!‬
It's nothing but shipwrecks!
‫هذه سفن محطّمة‬
It is a forest!
‫ذلك لأنّها غابة‬
Yeah, it is.
‫أجل‬
How are those related?!
‫وما علاقة هذا؟‬
On top of that, they're all sliced in half...
‫وكلّها مقسومة إلى النصف أيضًا...‬
Not again!
‫ثانيةً؟‬
Like I said, forests are full of all sorts of–
‫أخبرتك أنّه تحدث الكثير من الأشياء في الغابة...‬
I was wrong!
‫كلّا!‬
Hurry, full speed ahead! Hurry! Paddle, paddle! Go!
‫إلى الأمام بأقصى سرعة، إلى الأمام، جدّفا، جدّفا بسرعة، إلى الأمام!‬
Huh? What's going on?
‫ماذا، ما الخطب؟‬
A sickle monster!
‫وحش منجلي!‬
Watch out! There's another one!
‫لا ترخي دفاعك! هناك أخرى قادمة!‬
No... Not just one...!
‫كلّا، ليست واحدة فحسب‬
Paddle like hell!
‫جدّفا بأقصى ما تملكان!‬
What's trying to kill us now?!
‫ما هذا؟‬
Luffy, pay attention! Hit the brake!
‫راقب أين تذهب واضغط المكابح يا لوفي!‬
We're not gonna make it! Take the wheel, Usopp!
‫لا، لن نلحق، تولّ عجلة القيادة يا أوسوب‬
Gum-Gum...
‫فاكهة المطّاط‬ ‫غومو غومو نو‬
Luffy, what're you doing?! Eyes forward!
‫ماذا تفعل يا لوفي؟ صوّب نحو الأمام!‬
Just keep going straight!
‫تقدّم فحسب!‬
...Bazooka!
‫المدفع‬ ‫بازوكا‬
Dodged it!
‫تفاديناها‬
That was close!
‫كان ذلك وشيكًا!‬
We managed to evade it...
‫تفاديناها بطريقةٍ ما‬
but it's not looking good! We can't go back now!
‫ولكن هذه مصيبة! لن نستطيع العودة الآن!‬
We've come a long way from the entrance!
‫تقدمنا كثيرًا عن المدخل‬
Wanna get off here?
‫أتريد النزول هنا؟‬
Don't be stupid! I'd die!
‫لا تكن غبيًا، سأموت‬
Yeah, probably.
‫على الأرجح‬
What was that, a snake?!
‫ما هذا؟ ثعبان؟‬
A lamprey. So, a sky lamprey, I guess?
‫جلكي. أهو «جلكي سماوي»؟‬
One that big will do more than suck a little blood!
‫لن تكتفي بامتصاص دمائنا بحجمها هذا‬
What a neat forest!
‫يا لها من غابة شيّقة!‬
Neat, my butt! If this is our ordeal, I've already had enough!
‫ليست شيّقة! إن كانت هذه هي الطامة، فقد اكتفيت‬
But we've only just entered the forest.
‫دخلنا الغابة توًّا‬
We'll really be screwed if we stall or stop on this milky road...
‫سنواجه خطرًا كبيرًا إن توقفنا في نهر الغيم‬
Looks like our only choice is to keep moving!
‫لا نملك خيارًا سوى التقدّم‬
There he is!
‫خرج!‬
Zoro!
‫زورو!‬
He's gonna lose to the sky shark!
‫يتفوق القرش السماوي على زورو!‬
He went under again...
‫غطس ثانيةً...‬
Zoro isn't coming back up!
‫لم يصعد زورو بعد‬
Do you think... he got eaten?!
‫هل يمكن... أنّه أكله؟‬
Zoro was eaten!
‫اُلتهم زورو‬
If he were eaten, the clouds would turn red.
‫لو كان اُلتهم، لأصبحت الغيوم حمراء‬
Don't say such ominous things with a straight face, Robin!
‫كيف لكِ يا روبين التفوه بشيءٍ مخيف كهذا!‬
You're finished!
‫طفح الكيل!‬
This is bad...
‫يا إلهي...‬
Looks like swimming away is out of the question.
‫لا يبدو أن الهروب سباحةً خيارًا متاحًا لنا‬
Why'd you punch it?! I thought you were a swordsman.
‫ألكمتَ ذلك القرش رغم أنك سياف؟‬
Zoro's so strong!
‫إنّك قوي حقًّا يا زورو‬
I'm certain that this is the interior of Upper Yard.
‫لا شكّ أنّ هذا المكان داخل الساحة العليا‬
It's almost as if this is a sacrificial altar...
‫يبدو هذا المكان وكأنّه مذبح قرابين...‬
Now there's a giant!
‫ها قد ظهر عملاق!‬
No. That's a statue!
‫كلّا، هذا تمثال‬
Hey, but... it's totally a dead end.
‫ولكنّها نهاية مسدودة‬
No, there are four entrances!
‫كلّا، توجد أربع مداخل‬
And let me guess; each one leads to a different place.
‫هل تقود كلّ واحدةٍ إلى مكانٍ مختلف؟‬
"Ordeal of Swamp."
‫«طامة المستنقع»،‬
"Ordeal of Iron."
‫«طامة الحديد»،‬
"Ordeal of String."
‫«طامة الخيوط»،‬
"Ordeal of Balls."
‫«طامة الكرات»،‬
Can we go in any one of them?!
‫أيمكننا عبور أيٍّ منها؟‬
Is "God" trying to play games with us or something?
‫أيحاول الإله اللهو معنا؟‬
Four ordeals... Which one do we choose?
‫أربعة طامات... أيّها نختار؟‬
A second-degree crime, huh? Does God mean nothing to them?!
‫جريمة من الدرجة الثانية؟ من تظنون الإله؟‬
Go ahead... Choose. We'll gladly indulge you in any of them.
‫اختاروا طامتكم، سنسعد بتنفيذها‬
It's a sin to live in ignorance.
‫إنّه لإثمٌ أن يحيا المرء في الجهل‬
The means to attaining peace do not lead one to heaven.
‫سُبل السلام لا تفضي بالمرء إلى الجنة‬
Swamp!
‫المستنقع!‬
Iron!
‫الحديد!‬
String!
‫الخيوط!‬
Balls!
‫الكرات!‬
Choose an ordeal!
‫اختاروا طامتكم!‬
So what do we choose?
‫ماذا نفعل؟‬
Alright! Let's go with "Balls"!
‫حسنٌ، لِنختَر الكرات!‬
Why's that, Luffy?
‫لماذا يا لوفي؟‬
Because balls are fun!
‫لأنّها تبدو ممتعة‬
That's your reason?!
‫أهذا سببك؟‬
These are ordeals! They're not gonna be fun!
‫هذه طامات، يستحيل أن تكون ممتعة!‬
But I do agree with "Balls."
‫ولكنّي أوافقك على الكرات‬
It's the ordeal that sounds the least violent.
‫إنّها الوحيدة الّتي لا توحي بعنف‬
Then it's decided. But don't let your guard down.
‫حُسم الأمر، ولكن لا ترخي دفاعك‬
We're on God's Island, 10,000 meters in the sky!
‫إنّنا في جزيرة الإله، على ارتفاع 10,000 متر!‬
Anything could happen here!
‫لن أستغرب من أي أمرٍ يحدث‬
Let's go! Balls!
‫لنذهب إلى الكرات!‬
Hey, helmsman! Might wanna keep your eyes open!
‫ويحك، لا تغمض عينيك أيّها السائق‬
Open or closed, it's still pitch black!
‫المكان مظلم تمامًا حتى وإن فتحتها‬
Hey, is there other stuff like this?
‫ولكن أليس هذا شائعًا؟‬
Like what?
‫ماذا؟‬
So with only four entrances...
‫كانت هناك أربع مداخل، أليس كذلك؟‬
what if only one of them was the lucky one?!
‫ربما أحدها صحيح وأما الأخرى فخاطئة‬
Huh?! Don't say that kind of crap now!
‫ماذا؟ لا تقل هذا الآن!‬
What happens if we chose the wrong one?!
‫ما الذي سيحدث إن اخترنا مدخلًا خاطئًا؟‬
If it's the wrong one? Hmm...
‫إن أخطأنا... ربما...‬
Maybe we'll fall off the sky island?
‫ربما سنسقط من جزيرة السماء؟‬
We can't afford to fall off!
‫كفاك مزاحًا، محالٌ حدوث ذلك‬
It's 10,000 meters to the Blue Sea, you know!
‫نحن على ارتفاع 10,000 عن البحر الأزرق‬
This high up, 1,000 lives would flash before your eyes!
‫تستطيع تأمل حياتك عدّة مرات خلال هبوطك‬
It's too crazy to even think about!
‫إنّها فكرةٌ بالغة الجنون‬
Quit being dumbasses! That's obviously not gonna hap–
‫توقفا عن التفوه بالغباء، يستحيل أن يحدث هـ...‬
No way! You have got to be kidding me!
‫لا... مستحيل!‬
It wasn't just one! There's a whole swarm of sky sharks!
‫لم يكن سوى مقدّمة لسربٍ من القروش السماوية‬
We'd be here until nightfall if we fought every one of them.
‫سنظل حتى غروب الشمس إن واجهناهم واحدًا تلو الآخر‬
We'd never reach shore at that rate...
‫لن نبلغ الشاطئ إن استمررنا هكذا‬
But we can't just sit here, either.
‫ولا يمكننا البقاء هنا‬
That giant lobster brought us to one hell of a place...
‫أحضرنا ذلك السلطعون العملاق إلى مكانٍ لا يُصدّق‬
Do you suppose starving us here is "Divine Reckoning"?
‫هل تجويعنا هنا هو جزاءنا الإلهي؟‬
Would a god really do something so tasteless?
‫أيقوم الإله بأمورٍ سخيفةٍ كهذه؟‬
Hard to say. I've never met one.
‫لا أدري، فلم أقابله من قبل‬
This is bad...
‫هذا سيّئ‬
We can't set the boat in the water with the hull like this.
‫لا يمكننا أن نبحر وهيكل السفينة هكذا‬
Try to fix the ship somehow, Chopper.
‫حاول إصلاحها بطريقةٍ ما يا تشوبر‬
Huh? Me?! Okay...
‫ماذا؟ أنا؟ حسنًا...‬
Fix it? What are you up to?
‫يصلحها؟ أتخطط لشيءٍ ما؟‬
I've gotta get into this forest.
‫سأذهب إلى الغابة بطريقةٍ ما‬
For now, let's make this our base of operations.
‫لنجعل هذا المكان مركزًا لقيادة عملياتنا‬
I'm sure Luffy and the others are headed here to search for us.
‫لا بدّ وأن لوفي والبقية متوجهون إلى هنا للبحث عنّا‬
It's like they say, "If you get lost, stay put."
‫تعرفون ما يقال...‬
You need to stay put the most!
‫لا تبرح مكانك أنت بالأخصّ‬
Say, Zoro... you said you're going into the forest, but what for?
‫يا زورو، قلت إنك ستدخل الغابة، ماذا تنوي فعله؟‬
There's a god on this island, right? I'm gonna go meet him.
‫أليس الإله موجودًا على هذه الجزيرة؟ سأذهب لمقابلته‬
I'm telling you, that's a bad idea! What if you run into those freaks?!
‫توقف، ماذا ستفعل إن واجهت أولئك المخيفين؟‬
Good question. I guess it all depends on how they act.
‫لا أعلم... يعتمد ذلك على تصرفهم‬
Zoro... it's like you're mightier than a god...
‫يبدو زورو أعظم من الإله‬
He has priests on this island too, you know!
‫كهنته متواجدون في هذه الجزيرة لعلمك!‬
We can't make a god angry! It's common sense, you know!
‫لا ينبغي لنا أن نُغضب الإله، فهذه من البديهيات‬
Sorry, but...
‫أعتذر ولكن...‬
I've never once prayed to a god.
‫لم أدعُ الإله مطلقًا‬
So cool!
‫رائع!‬
I don't believe in them either, so I don't owe this god a thing.
‫ولا أؤمن به أيضًا، لذلك لا أدينُ له بشيء‬
Oh, mighty God!
‫يا إلهي، ما لي به من صلة فلا تعاقبني‬
That vine looks usable.
‫تبدو هذه الكرمة قابلة للاستخدام‬
You're right, good idea.
‫معك حق، فكرة جيدة‬
Mind if I join you, Mr. Swordsman?
‫هل يمكنني أن أرافقك أيّها السيد السياف؟‬
Huh? Sure, but don't go slowing me down!
‫ماذا؟ لا بأس، ولكن لا تُعيقيني‬
Hold on!
‫لحظة، إلى أين ستذهبين يا روبين؟‬
Look at this.
‫انظروا لهذا‬
This altar was built at least 1,000 years ago.
‫مرّت ألف سنة على الأقل منذ أن بُني هذا المذبح‬
– At least... 1,000 years?!
‫أ-ألف سنة؟‬
Historical findings like this make me prickle with excitement!
‫الأشياء التاريخية كهذه تجعل جسدي يرتعش‬
Where there is a rich history, there will be an abundance of relics.
‫حيثما وُجد تاريخٌ عريق، وُجدت آثارٌ زاخرة‬
Perhaps even a few jewels that would help pay for ship repairs.
‫أراهن أنّنا سنجد حتى بعض المجوهرات لإفادة سفينتنا‬
I'm coming too!
‫سآتي أيضًا!‬
Really?! Even after you were so scared?!
‫ماذا؟ رغم أنكِ كنتِ خائفة جدًّا؟‬
It's for investigating history!
‫من أجل البحث التاريخي!‬
Those are belly signs...
‫تحولت عيناها إلى بيري...‬
Do you have to make that sound?
‫أهذه صيحة العزيمة؟‬
Robin is amazing!
‫روبين مذهلة!‬
She did it so easily...
‫فعلتها بسهولة...‬
This might be a bit too high up...
‫أنا على ارتفاع شاهق‬
It's about fifty meters! If you slip, you'll die!
‫إنكِ على ارتفاع خمسين مترًا، ستموتين إن أخفقتِ‬
Stop saying morbid things!
‫لا تقولي شيئًا مخيفًا كهذا!‬
I really am a goner if I fall!
‫ستحلّ نهايتي حقًّا إن سقطت‬
Nami...
‫نامي...‬
T-Too fast! I can't stop!
‫هـ-هذا سريع، سريع جدًّا، لا أستطيع التوقف‬
See? You have courage.
‫إنّكِ شجاعة‬
I apologize for the inconvenience.
‫أعتذر عن التسبب بالمتاعب‬
Not at all.
‫على الإطلاق‬
That's because you didn't go, "Aah-eeh-ah-eeh-aaaaaah!"
‫هذا لأنّكِ لم تصرخي مثلي‬
Is that the issue here?!
‫حقًّا؟‬
This certainly is a big forest...
‫إنها غابة كبيرة حقًّا...‬
Okay, Chopper! You're in charge of the ship!
‫حسنٌ إذًا يا تشوبر، أنت مسؤولٌ عن السفينة،‬
You've got this!
‫نعتمد عليك‬
We'll be back soon!
‫سنعود بسرعة‬
Right! Be careful, everyone! Come back safe!
‫أجل، توخوا الحذر جميعًا، عودوا بسلام‬
I guess Nami will be okay since she has Zoro and Robin.
‫ستكون نامي بخير بما أنّها مع زورو وروبين‬
I'm too scared to go...
‫أمّا أنا خائف ولا أقوى على الذهاب‬
Everyone is so brave and amazing!
‫جميعهم شجعان ومذهلون‬
I wonder if I'll be brave someday, too...
‫هل سأغدو شجاعًا يومًا يا تُرى؟‬
Anyway, I'll do everything I can now!
‫على أيّ حال، سأفعل كل ما بوسعي الآن‬
Taking care of the ship by myself in a dangerous forest
‫أن أكون مسؤولًا عن السفينة وحدي في هذه الغابة الخطرة...‬
is proof that everyone has faith in me!
‫هو دليل على ثقة رفاقي بي‬
I gotta do my best!
‫عليّ أن أبذل جهدي!‬
That's right! I'm all alone in this dangerous place–
‫صحيح! أنا وحدي تمامًا في هذا المكان الخطر‬
I'm the one in the most danger!
‫أنا الأكثر عرضة للخطر!‬
We're alive...
‫نجونا...‬
I seriously thought we were gonna fall 10,000 meters...
‫اعتقدت أنّنا سنسقط من 10,000 متر حقًّا...‬
You freaked Usopp out with that nonsense, Luffy!
‫أفزعته لأنّك تقول أشياء مضللة يا لوفي‬
That was scary! I thought I was gonna die!
‫خفت، ظننت أنّي سأموت‬
But still, what is this place?
‫ولكن ما هذا المكان؟‬
They're balls. Definitely balls.
‫إنّها كرات...‬
They're little balls of island cloud...
‫إنها كُرات صغيرة من غيوم الجزيرة‬
Awesome! They're like big snow!
‫مذهل، كأنها ثلج عملاق!‬
What a weird place! It's so neat!
‫يا له من مكان غريب، هذا شيّق‬
The milky road leads above the trees...
‫يمتدّ نهر الغيم إلى أعلى الشجر...‬
But what part of this is an ordeal?
‫ولكن أين الطامة بهذا؟‬
Who knows?
‫لا أدري‬
It'd be great if there's nothing at all, but I doubt that's the case.
‫سيكون من الأفضل ألّا يكون هناك شيء، ولكن أشكّ بهذا‬
Maybe we did get the lucky entrance!
‫ربما اخترنا المدخل الصحيح‬
I bet if we chose one of the others, we'd be in trouble right about now!
‫كنا لنتعرض لمصيبة لو أنّنا اخترنا أحد المداخل الأخرى‬
Y-Yeah! You might be right!
‫صـ-صحيح، قد تكون محقًّا!‬
Right?!
‫أليس كذلك؟‬
You idiots, don't let your guard down!
‫لا ترخيا دفاعكما أيّها الغبيان‬
Would they really let criminals off without a hitch?
‫هل تعتقدان أنّهم سيسمحون لمجرمين بالتجول كما يشاؤون؟‬
Think about it!
‫فكّرا قليلًا‬
There might be traps like earlier...
‫قد تكون هناك فخاخ مثل السابق...‬
Stay alert!
‫توخيا الحذر‬
Let's just keep moving...
‫لنتقدم على أيّ حال‬
I'm thirsty! Let's have some tea!
‫أشعر بالعطش، لنشرب شاي!‬
Huh? Yeah, let's! Open the rice crackers in your bag!
‫نعم، لنفعل هذا، افتح كعك الأرز الموجود في حقيبتك‬
Oh, good idea!
‫فكرة رائعة‬
You sons of...
‫أيّها الوغدان...‬
C'mon, just one rice cracker!
‫لا بأس بكعكة أرز واحدة!‬
Yeah! Let's eat, let's eat!
‫أجل! لنأكل، لنأكل‬
Knock it off! Listen, I'm gonna keep steering.
‫لا، استمعا، سأستمر بالقيادة‬
You guys keep watch on both sides!
‫لذا راقبا الميمنة والميسرة جيّدًا‬
It took us really high up at some point...
‫وصلنا إلى مكان عالٍ قبل أن ندرك‬
But it's strange...
‫ولكن هذا غريب‬
There are four priests, so I assumed each entrance would lead us to one...
‫قالوا أنّ هناك أربعة كهنة، لذا افترضت أنّ كل مدخل يقود إلى أحدهم‬
but I guess not.
‫ولكن لا يبدو كذلك‬
Hey, Usopp! Pass!
‫يا أوسوب، مرّر!‬
Okay! I got it! Pass!
‫حسنًا، أمسكتُ بها، مرّر!‬
I told you to keep watch!
‫أخبرتكما أن تراقبا‬
A snake!
‫ثعبان!‬
You jerk! Beat it!
‫أيّها الوغد، ابتعد عن هنا‬
That was a surprise! Why would...?
‫فاجأني، لماذا؟‬
Sanji! Look out! There's another cloud!
‫سانجي، أمامك غيمة!‬
Kick it far away!
‫اركلها إلى مكانٍ بعيد‬
Dammit! Are all these floating things snake eggs?!
‫سحقًا، أكلّ هذه الأشياء العائمة ثعابين؟‬
– This isn't good...
‫هذا سيّئ...‬
What's the deal with these balls?!
‫ما خطب هذه الكرات؟‬
There's no telling what's inside!
‫تطلّعوا لما سيخرج منها‬
These clouds are called surprise clouds!
‫اسم هذه الغيوم هو «الغيوم المباغتة»‬
Surprise clouds?!
‫الغيوم المباغتة؟‬
Heso!
‫هيسو!‬
Who's there?!
‫من أنت؟‬
Thank you for choosing my Ordeal of Balls!
‫شكرًا لاختياركم طامة الكرات خاصتي‬
Satori of the Forest Skypiea Priest
‫«ساتوري» الغابة‬ ‫أحد كهنة سكايبيا‬
What's with the dumpling freak?
‫من وغد الدانغو هذا؟‬
Don't tell me he's a priest?!
‫أيعقل أن يكون كاهنًا؟‬
You're the ball in the Ordeal of Balls?!
‫إذًا فأنت الكرة في طامة الكرات؟‬
Quit dancing around! Who the hell are you?!
‫كفاك رقصًا! من أنت أيها الوغد؟‬
Wow, he seems dumber than I expected...
‫إنّه أكثر بلاهةً مما ظننت‬
Didn't Nami and the old guy say they were really strong?
‫ألم تقل نامي والعم أنّهم أقوياء جدًّا؟‬
Hey! Dumpling!
‫أيّها الدانغو!‬
Nami's group had better be safe!
‫هل نامي-سان والبقية بخير؟‬
You mean the sacrifices?
‫أتعني القرابين؟‬
If so, I wouldn't know! But they'll die if they're left alone!
‫إن كان كذلك، فلا علم لي، لكنهم سيموتون إن تُركوا وحدهم‬
And even if they escape, they're still going to die!
‫وإن فرّوا، سيموتون في النهاية!‬
Say what?!
‫ماذا قلت؟‬
You should worry about yourselves.
‫عليكم أن تقلقوا على أنفسكم‬
In case you didn't realize it, you'll need to defeat me to continue ahead!
‫لعلمكم، يتوجب عليكم هزيمتي لتتمكنوا من التقدم‬
Okay, Luffy! Here he comes! Get 'im!
‫ها قد أتى يا لوفي، أجهز عليه‬
Alright! I'll knock him out of the air!
‫حسنًا! سأطيح به!‬
Gum-Gum...
‫فاكهة المطّاط‬ ‫غومو غومو نو‬
Oh, you're going to stretch?
‫هل ستمتد؟‬
...Pistol!
‫المسدس‬ ‫بيستول‬
No way!
‫لا يعقل!‬
Luffy!
‫لوفي!‬
Luffy?! Hey! You're okay, right?!
‫لوفي! أنت بخير، أليس كذلك؟‬
A regular hit shouldn't affect you!
‫لا ينبغي للضربات العادية أن تنفع ضدك‬
A regular hit?
‫ضربة عادية؟‬
This is a bit different from a regular hit!
‫هذه مختلفة قليلًا عن الضربة العادية‬
The hell do you mean by that?!
‫ما المختلف بشأنها؟‬
An upward kick with the right leg...
‫ركلة علوية بالرجل اليمنى...‬
Collier– What?!
‫ركلة العنـ... ماذا؟!‬
Those with enough discipline and training are given the power of mantra.
‫المانترا تعني حبل القلب‬ ‫تُمنَح قوة المانترا لمن تحلّى بالانضباط والتدريب‬
Impossible! He predicted my movements?!
‫مستحيل، أتنبّا بتحركاتي؟‬
Sanji!
‫سانجي!‬
It is different from a hit!
‫إنّها مختلفة عن الضربة العادية!‬
Impact!
‫الصدمة‬ ‫إمباكت‬
The shock destroys the body from the inside!
‫تُدمّر الصدمة الجسد من الداخل!‬
D-Dammit! Sanji! Usopp!
‫سـ-سحقًا! سانجي، أوسوب!‬
Yeah, I'm alright... But what the hell was that?!
‫أجل، أنا بخير... ماذا فعل ذلك الوغد؟‬
No idea at all...! He's a mystery!
‫لا أدري، إنّه غامض‬
My name is Satori!
‫اسمي ساتوري‬
I am one of the priests of the almighty God Enel!
‫أنا أحد كهنة الإله العظيم إنيل!‬
I own the vearth in these Lost Woods.
‫أملك «فيرث» غابة الأوهام هذه‬
Lost Woods?
‫غابة الأوهام؟‬
Yes!
‫نعم‬
That is what we call this forest!
‫هذه الغابة!‬
And...
‫وأيضًا...‬
your boat will be lost within it!
‫ما سيضيع فيها هو قاربكم!‬
The boat is taking off!
‫إنّ القارب يتحرك!‬
Your boat will now speed along the milky road at random
‫سيسير قاربكم على نهر الغيم عشوائيًّا،‬
and eventually leave through this forest's only exit!
‫وسيشق طريقه إلى خارج الغابة من خلال مخرجها الوحيد‬
I'm sure you realize it, but losing a dial boat
‫من المفترض أنكم تدركون هذا، فقدانكم لقارب الدايل...‬
is the same as losing your way to the sacrificial altar.
‫يعني ضلّ الطريق نحو مذبح القرابين‬
So you must find and board the boat before that happens.
‫لذا عليكم أن تجدوا القارب وتركبوه قبل حدوث هذا‬
Of course, these countless surprise clouds and I will not allow that.
‫وبالطبع، أنا وهذه الغيوم المباغتة التي لا تُحصى، لن نسمح بحدوث ذلك‬
Welcome to the sacred ground of Upper Yard!
‫مرحبًا بكم في الأرض المقدّسة، الساحة العليا!‬
This is the Lost Woods' Ordeal of Balls, which has a 10 percent survival rate!
‫هذه هي طامة كرات غابة الأوهام، والتي يُقدّر معدل النجاة فيها عشرة في المئة‬
A 10 percent survival rate?!
‫معدل النجاة... عشرة في المئة؟‬